the best part about working in
recruitment is bringing in the Future
Leaders of our
[Music]
organization I learned about manual life
through kind of its oncampus events and
info sessions in terms of like the
culture that manual life has it is
really different everyone that I've
interacted with has been extremely
supportive to my personal growth Journey
all the managers uh and and my BP we
always have one-on ones we kind of
always get continuous feedback even when
I was a cop I was often encouraged to um
really expand on my current skill set to
take on larger projects to think big I
do think that I've grown a lot in like
my technical skills I think what makes
man you live a great place to work is
the diversity here and again the support
from everyone everyone around here has
different experiences and backgrounds
it's nice to kind of gain different
perspectives and be able to work in a
global work place the people in the
culture they really make it exciting to
come to work there's always a lot of new
things to work on no day is the same the
feeling of about being excited that
there's so much more new things to learn
never changed since I was a co-op
student I feel um excited and
motivated really because the the people
that I work with and the friends that
I've made along the way main Life as a
company is just great for foster
inclusivity and their dedication to
Innovation and just commitment to just
improving everything they have is a
great place to work